That’s right.
I sent him
away to gain experience.
Five years, all he does
is hammer rocks in the mines.
A pack of blind idiots.
Lord Severin is the sun itself.
How dare you offend him?
Fine.
Both your families
are banished from Emeraldstone.
What?
Lord Darren, you’re banishing us?
Not just these two.
Who else, my lord?
Everyone in this
cathedral who came for
me today will pay the price.
Who the hell do
you think you are?!
Exactly.
Every single person here outranks you.
What gives you the
right to spout such nonsense?
What?
You want to
go to war with
the iron cavalry
of Black Raven City?
House Carter stands
behind the Morellan family!
They're all-powerful!
The Morellan family backs you?
Of course.
The Morellan family leads the
Four Great Families of Golantis.
Next to them,
your little Black Raven City
is just a pile of shit!
Lord Darren, has Severin bewitched
you with some kind of spell?
What are you saying?
Lord Darren,
I was engaged to him for three years.
I know him best.
He's mediocre and useless.
All he does is talk big.
Promises to amaze me, give me
the most expensive crown in Golantis.
Three years later,
he's still a failure.
Lady Livia, I’m
sorry, but
Everything Lord Severin
said is the truth.